印象电影
您的私人影院
伦敦  英国
人们常说如果你想知晓未来
They say if you want a glimpse of the future...
只需回首过去
Just look behind you.
我原以为这都是胡说八道
I used to think that was bollocks.
现在我明白了
Now I realize...
人永远逃不出历史的宿命
you can't outrun the past.
在我们还小的时候
When we were kids...
你总是向街坊里的恶霸寻衅
You'd start fights with the toughest bastards in the yard.
而我总是那个
But I was the one...
挺身而出 解决他们的人
who were to step in and finish them.
好好休息吧 弟弟
Rest now, little brother.
让我来再为你收拾一次残局
While I settle your one last score.
照顾好我弟弟
Take care of my brother.
他如果有什么三长两短
Anything happens to him...
我会回来找你们算账
I'll come back looking for you.
范·迪塞尔
保罗·沃克
道恩
强森
米歇尔·罗德里格兹
泰瑞斯·吉布森
卢达·克里斯
乔丹娜·布鲁斯
杰曼·翰苏
托尼·贾
给你
Here.
拿好了
Hold this.
龙达·鲁西
娜塔莉·伊曼纽尔
库尔特·拉塞尔
杰森·斯坦森
翻译 neoKe  夏洛
翻译 清明 雾响子
翻译 Mark 娄小胖
校对 Peach
校对 Jophy
校对 娄小胖
总校 娄小胖 Jophy
特效 时轴 CAS
压制 hhjie
总监  娄小胖
速度与激情7
字幕由SSK字幕组倾情译制
仅供学习，勿用于商，转载请注明出处，版权归片方所有
说吧 多姆 你到底要带我去哪里
Come on, Dom, so where are you taking me?
他们说空旷的公路有助你思考
They say an open road helps you think...
关于你去过哪里
about where you've been...
要到哪里去的问题
where you're going.
你真的一点都不记得了吗
So you don't remember any of this yet?
这不公平
It's not fair.
你知道我失忆了
You know I don't.
你到底想带我去看什么
So what is it exactly that you're trying to show me?
就是那儿
That.
极速大赛
Race Wars.
我们以前参加过这个吗
We used to come here?
何止是参加
Come here?
是我们创造了它
We invented it.
转速控制在九千以下
Keep it under 9000 rpms.
用不了两百米这小子的活塞就会报废
Kid's gonna fire his pistons after the first 200.
你知道这不是我的风格 不飙宁死 不是吗
You know that's not my style, I got to ride or die, right?
这次不提死字好吗
How about you just ride on this one.
准备好了吗
Are you ready?
我知道你已经跃跃欲试了
I know you're ready!
出发
Go!
干得漂亮
Nice job!
嗨
Hey!
这不就是传说中的女孩吗
That's the girl I heard so much about.
你之前跑哪去了 死而复生的女孩
Where you been at, ghost girl?
就是那个女孩
That's the girl...
死而复生的女孩
Ghost girl...
莱蒂 你搞什么鬼
Letty, what the hell?
靠 多姆 你那妞的勾拳还是如此生猛
Damn, Dom! Your girl's still got that swing, homie.
是你太弱了好吗
You never could take a punch.
好吧 好吧
Right, right.
嘿 兄弟 很高兴你回来了 见到你真开心
Hey, man, I'm glad you're back, man. It's good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你 赫克托
Good to see you, Hektor.
到啦 我们赶上了 杰克
Alright. We made it, Jack.
-是的 我们赶上了 -耶 我们赶上啦
- Yeah, we made it! - Yeah, we made it.
现在我要找一下开门的按钮
I just gotta, find that door button.
儿子 你知道开门的按钮在哪儿吗
Buddy where's the door button at? Do you know?
-嘿 -嘿
- Hey. - Hey.
是啊 早该想到了
Yeah, of course.
我还是个新手
I'm new to this.
是啊 你看上去就不像是开保姆车的
Yeah, you don't seem like the minivan type.
确实不是
No, not exactly.
嘿 儿子 你还没跟我击掌呢 等等
Hey buddy you didn't give me a high-five? Wait, wait, wait.
击一下掌 好啦 非常好 乖儿子
High-five! All right! Yeah, buddy.
太谢谢你了
Appreciate it, thank you.
别担心 你很快就会适应的
Don't worry, you'll get used to this in no time.
是啊 这才是我担心的
Yeah, that's what I'm afraid of.
当我第一次见到它的时候
First time I saw this...
我觉得它很可笑
I thought it was kind of funny.
现在发现 可笑的是我自己
I guess now, the joke's on me.
你要做什么
What are you doing?
做我早就该做的事
What I should've done a long time ago.
住手
Stop!
看看它
Look at it.
这就是事实
It's the truth.
莱蒂西亚
奥尔蒂斯
挚爱的女儿 姐妹
和永远的朋友
生于1983年9月7日
卒于2009年5月30日
挚爱的女儿 姐妹
和永远的朋友
这是我失忆的那一天
That's the date that I lost my memory.
是莱蒂死去的那一天
That's the date that Letty died.
也是我重生的那一天
And I was born.
不
No.
你从来没有死去过
You never died.
你知道你这么看我 我有多难受吗
Do you know how hard it is for me when you look at me?
你透过十五年的记忆看着我
And you see me through 15 years of memories?
透过那些所有我们拥有的美好瞬间
Every beautiful moment we've ever had.
我能从你的眼睛里看到它们
I see it in your eyes.
但我什么都给不了你
I can't give that to you.
我什么都没有
I got nothing.
你有我
You got me.
而你只有一部分的我
And you've got only a piece of me.
我必须要去找回自己
I have to find myself.
为了我自己
For me.
再见了 多姆
Goodbye, Dom.
外交安全局 洛杉矶分局
已抓捕
你很失望吧
You're disappointed, aren't you?
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
上一次抓捕行动
The last arrest.
太简单了 目标几乎是坐等被抓的
It was too easy. Target didn't even run.
噢 还好啦
Ah, it's okay.
给我个拷手铐的机会
Gives me a chance to hit the iron.
也让我练习一下盖章的技巧
Also, lets me work on my stamping skills.
你撒谎技术太差了
You're a terrible liar.
明天见 老大
See you tomorrow, boss.
-明天见 -别待太晚
- I'll see you then. - Don't stay too late.
我想待多久就待多久 妹子
I'll stay as long as I want, woman.
就知道你会这么说
I knew you'd say that.
埃琳娜
Elena?
这是什么
What's this?
这是你要的推荐信
It's the letter of recommendation you asked for.
一字一句都是我的肺腑之言
Just know I meant every word in there.
谢谢 霍布斯
Thanks, Hobbs.
谢谢你所做的一切
Thanks for everything.
拜托 现在也太煽情了吧
Come on, way too sentimental right now.
回家吧 晚安
Get home. Good night.
好的 晚安啦
Okay. Bye.
马上就好
Just one sec.
你肯定不是技术部门的人 所以你最好老实交代
You sure as hell ain't the IT guy so you better start talking...
省得我用六种不同的方式废了你的手指
before I break that finger six different ways...
再把它们塞到你身体上永远晒不到太阳的地方
and stick it straight right where the sun doesn't shine.
霍布斯探员 对吗
Agent Hobbs, right?
正是在下
That's right.
我也是这个星球上
I'm also the last man on
你最不该黑进他电脑的人
Earth whose computer you wanna be hacking into.
你惹错人了 孩子
You just earned yourself a dance with the devil, boy.
你被捕了
You're under arrest.
像我所说的 我是来查那个让我弟弟致残的团队
Like I said, I'm here for the team that crippled my brother.
没有什么所谓的团队
There ain't no goddamn team.
只有一个人 而他就站在你面前
It was just one man, and he's standing right in front of you.
那位女士说的对
The lady was right.
你撒谎技术太差了
You are a terrible liar.
去他妈的技术人员
Goddamn IT guys.
霍布斯
Hobbs!
掩护我
On me!
埃琳娜
Elena!
霍布斯
Hobbs?
Hobbs!
文件传输完毕
好啦儿子 再不走就要迟到啦
Alright buddy, we gotta go or we'll be late.
快来
Come on.
好
Okay, uhh.
你觉得怎么样
What do you think?
到学校门口由你来踩刹车
Parking brake slide right up to the school?
妈咪在哪里
Where's mommy?
不知道 还在上面吧 她马上来了
I don't know. She's up there. She's coming.
噢
Oh.
好啦 小心你的头
Watch your head.
多姆 你有个包裹
Dom, you have a package out here.
东京寄来的
From Tokyo.
东京吗
Tokyo?
韩想干什么 给我换个涡轮增压器吗
What's Han trying, to convert me over to a turbo charger?
准备好了吗
You ready?
我们要出发啦
There we go.
喂儿子 车是不会飞的
Hey buddy, cars don't fly.
噢 车不会飞
Hey, cars don't fly.
这辆会的 对吧
This one did, huh?
开保姆车的布莱恩
Brian in a minivan.
世界真的是变了
Things have changed.
他很纠结 多姆
He's struggling, Dom.
他不想让我看到
He doesn't want me to see it...
但我能看的出来 这种平淡的家庭生活对他来说是牵绊
but the white picket fence is like an anchor for him. I can tell.
有天晚上我试着跟他聊 你知道他说什么吗
I tried to talk to him the other night. Do you know what he said?
他怀念的不是美女 不是跑车
He doesn't miss the girls. He doesn't miss the cars.
而是枪林弹雨的生活
He misses the bullets.
让他慢慢适应吧 给他点时间
Let him settle in. Give him time.
九个月听起来够吗
How does nine months sound?
我又怀孕了
I'm having another baby.
你还没告诉他 对吧
And you didn't tell him, did you?
你得告诉他
You gotta tell him.
我不想他对这种生活失望
I don't want him to be disappointed with this life.
和我一起的生活
With me.
他永远都不会对你失望的
He will never be disappointed with you.
你是他今生最好的礼物
You're the best thing that's ever happened to him.
谢谢
Thank you.
喂
Yeah?
多米尼克·多雷托
Dominic Toretto.
你不认识我
You don't know me.
但很快就会认识了
You're about to.
私人号码
东京 日本
趴下
Get down!
杰克
Jack!
圣
心
医
院
锁骨粉碎 腿部骨折
Shattered his collarbone, fractured his leg in two places.
他今天早上才清醒过来
He only regained consciousness this morning.
睁开眼第一句话就是 把多姆找来
First thing he said was, "Get me Dom".
他就在里面
He's in there.
你还好吗
You okay?
我没事
I'm fine.
他在等你 进去吧
He's waiting. Let's go.
重症
监护
病房
看我把谁给你带来了
Got something for you.
你要的文件
Your files.
谢谢
Thank you.
你冒着生命危险拯救这个世界
You risk life and limb to save the free world...
而他们就这么对你吗
and what do they give you?
果冻配七十年代的老掉牙电视剧
Jell-O and a bad 70's TV show.
你知道吗 这还是有好处的
Y'know, it's got its perks.
海绵浴也不是那么糟糕
Sponge baths ain't that bad.
老爸
Dad!
不好意思 宝贝
I'm sorry, baby.
老爸是怎么一回事
Dad?
宝贝儿 我来给你介绍一下
Honey, I want to introduce you to somebody.
他是 呃
He's a, uhh...
他是位老朋友
He's an old friend.
快去打个招呼
Go on and say hello.
多米尼克·多雷托 对吗
Dominic Toretto, right?
我爸爸说 他曾经把你打得屁滚尿流
My dad said, he kicked your ass once.
小女孩 注意你的用词
Youny lady, watch your mouth.
你老爸止疼药吃多了 他记不清这段历史了
Your dad's having some pain meds.I can understand that his history is a little hazy
我深表怀疑
I doubt it.
好了 宝贝儿 我和多雷托谈事儿的时候 你跟埃琳娜去吃点东西 听见了吗
Alright, darling, that's enough. I want you to go get something to eat with Elena while me and Toretto have a talk. Hear me?
走吧 小宝贝 去吃点心吧
Come on lady. Let's get some cookies.
是谁干的
Who did this?
你还记得欧文·肖吗
You remember Owen Shaw?
印象电影
SSK•FanSub
那个我们毁了半个伦敦才抓到的人
The one we tore half of London down trying to get.
印象电影 您的私人影院
这次呢
Well...
轮到他的混蛋哥哥了
This is his big, bad brother.
看看这个
Take a look at this.
通缉令
德卡德 · 肖
戴克·肖
Deckard Shaw
英国特种部队的杀手
British Special Forces assassin.
他就是那种特别的资产
The kind of unique asset...
所有政府都不会承认曾经雇佣过他
that no government would ever admit to employing.
黑色行动的小伙子们
Black Ops boys.
更糟 他们创造了个怪物
Worse. They created a monster.
先前他们认为肖是有必要存在的恶魔 直到后来
They felt Shaw was a necessary evil until eventually...
他们觉得他是不必要的了
they decided he was unnecessary.
那些领导者们觉得他知道得有点太多了
The powers that be, felt that he knew just a little bit too much.
资产变成了负担
The asset became a liability.
所以他们派出了二十个精英杀手解决他
So they sent in 20 elite operatives to retire him.
而他们失败了
And they missed.
那已经是六年前了 在那之后肖就销声匿迹了
That was 6 years ago and Shaw's been a ghost ever since.
直到现在
Until now.
我要怎样才能找到他
How do I find him?
官方回答是 不要去找他
The official answer is: you don't.
他杀了韩
He killed Han.
还差点杀了我家人
Almost killed my family.
他也差点把我装进了裹尸袋里
He also tried to put me in a body bag, too.
所以等我出院后
Which is why when I get out,
一定要狠狠收拾他
I'm gonna put a hurt on him so bad...
让他后悔自己来到了这个世界上
he's gonna wish his mother had kept her legs closed.
但是在那之前 我给你的官方回答是
But until then, my official answer to you...
什么都不要做
is stand down.
你知道我做不到的
Now you know I can't do that.
我确实了解你 多姆
I do know you, Dom.
所以作为兄弟我要给你这个答案
Which is why now I give you a brother to brother answer.
做你想做的
You do whatever it is you gotta do.
等你找到那个狗娘养的
When you find that sumbitch...
帮我一个忙
Just do me one favor.
什么
What's that?
别失手了
Don't miss.
蒙特克里斯托 多米尼加共和国
谢谢你收留我们 曼多
Thank you so much for letting us stay, Mando.
希望不会给你带来麻烦
I hope it's not a problem.
如果是多姆要在两天后被安全送到里约
Listen, Dom needed a safe delivered to Rio in two days.
那才叫麻烦
That was a problem.
而在多米尼加共和国招待他的家人
Hosting his family in the Dominican Republic,
简直就像是在度假
that is vacation.
如果有什么人在这里找你们麻烦
Anyone messes with you here...
那他就是在跟整个国家作对
they're messing with the entire country.
你们会很安全的
You'll be safe.
是 他们在这里 我亲自去机场把他们接来了
Yeah, they're here. I picked them up myself at the airport.
等下 你哥哥找你
Hold on. Your brother.
多姆
Dom.
嗯 米娅 是我
Yeah, Mia, it's me.
你那边怎么样了
How's it going there?
我们在曼多家 这地方就像座堡垒
We're at Mando's. This place is like a fortress.
你真该见见布莱恩 他完全就开启了联邦调查局模式
You should see Brian. He's in full FBI mode.
他在曼多的车库里建了个监控中心什么的
He built a surveillance hub in Mando's garage and everything.
你呢 找到找我们麻烦的人了吗
What about you? Did you find out who's after us?
在伦敦种下的恶果似乎跟过来了
Looks like the sins of London have followed us home.
那个臭小子知道好消息了有什么反应
How did Buster take the news?
我不能告诉他
I can't tell him.
如果他知道孩子的事 他就会跟我们一起待在这里
If he knew about the baby, he'd stay here with us.
而现在发生了这些事 你需要他在你身边
And with all that's going on, you're gonna need him by your side.
好好看着他 保证他的安全
Just watch out for him. Keep him safe.
然后一起回家来
And come home together.
告诉布莱恩两天后在洛杉矶见
Tell Brian I'll see him in LA in two days.
你要去哪儿
Where are you going?
东京
Tokyo.
我要把韩带回家
I'm bringing Han home.
当局仍在努力调查
Authorities are still trying to determine...
不到三十六小时前
the motive behind this daring attack here at the office...
对位于洛杉矶市中心的
of the US Diplomatic Security Service in downtown Los Angeles...
美国外交安全局的攻击的动机
less than 36 hours ago.
证据仍在收集当中
Facts are still coming in...
但可以确定的是
but what is known is the
嫌疑人进了大楼的第四层
suspect entered the building's 4th floor...
嘿
Hey.
-你还好吗 -嗯
- You okay? - Yeah.
这家伙真是残忍
This guy's just, relentless.
所以多姆需要你
That's why Dom needs you.
你们俩要找到他 并阻止他
You two need to find this guy and you need to stop him...
别让他对我们的家人造成更大的伤害
before he does any more damage to our family.
只是
I just...
我搞砸了那么多事情
I've screwed up so many things.
我无法忍受自己把你我的幸福生活也搞砸
I couldn't live with myself if I screwed this up, too.
不会的
You won't.
我相信你
I believe in you.
我相信我们 这就够了
I believe in us. That's all that matters.
我爱你 布莱恩
I love you, Brian.
我也爱你 宝贝
Love you, baby.
答应我 这件事过了以后 我们就收手
Just promise me. After this, we're done.
不再接工作 不再有敌人
No more jobs, no more enemies.
回到我们身边
Come back to us.
我不会让你失望的 米娅
I won't let you down, Mia.
我知道
I know.
东京 日本
嘿 肖恩
Hey yo, Sean!
嗨 来看看这家伙
Hey, check this out, man.
这家伙想要参加新的甩尾王比赛
This dude over here wanna race the new DK.
今晚不行 蠢蛋
Not tonight, Twinkie.
他说他认识韩
He said he knew Han.
韩说你开很快 但没想到你真的那么快
Han said you was fast, but not that damn fast.
谁说美国老爷超跑不能漂移
Who said American muscle can't drift?
韩说过他从后视镜里看到他把对手甩在身后
Han mentioned he left his enemies in his rear view.
他很少聊这些
He never talked about it much.
他总是玩得很谨慎
Always playing it close to the vest.
我们在事故现场找到了一些东西
We found a couple of things by the crash.
也没留下多少东西
Wasn't much left.
吉赛尔
Gisele.
对了
Yeah.
还有个东西
There's one more thing.
我找到了这个
I found this.
这对他肯定有重要意义
Must've meant something to him.
如果你找到杀死韩的那家伙
When you find the guy that killed Han...
你打算怎么做
What are you going to do?
难以用语言表达
Words ain't even been invented yet.
人们说如果住进对方的心里
They say to live in the hearts of those we leave behind...
即使死亡也无法分开彼此
is not to die.
但他葬送了你
But he put you in his grave.
如今我也要亲手葬送他
So now I'll do the same to him.
我不能承受更多的葬礼了
I can't do no more funerals.
一开始是韩
First, Han...
现在霍布斯也倒下了 我们所有人
Now Hobbs is laid out, of all people.
都被盯上了
We're being hunted.
你知道他现在正在某个地方盯着我们 对吧
You know he's out there somewhere watching, right?
希望如此
I hope so.
这说明他离我们很近
That means he's close.
答应我 布莱恩
Just promise me, Brian.
不要再有葬礼了
No more funerals.
只剩最后一场了
Just one more.
他的葬礼
His.
你不该去招惹一个男人的家人
You never should've messed with a man's family.
我对你弟弟说过一样的话
I told your brother the same thing.
加固了底盘
Reinforced your chassis.
就像拳手戴着厚重的手套参加比赛一样
Just like going into the ring with weighted gloves.
你错了 我不是来玩的
Your mistake. I'm not here to play games.
明白吗 你跟我
See, you and me...
我们是不同世界的人
We're from different worlds.
相信我 我见过的事情
Trust me, I've seen a lot
比你所见过的要残酷得多
meaner streets than the ones you're used to.
那你可站好了
Stick around.
接下来会更残酷
It's gonna get a lot meaner.
你以为这是街头斗殴吗
You think this was gonna be a street fight?
趴下
On the ground!
立刻
Now!
放开他否则我就开枪了
Drop him or I will drop you!
哇 哇
Woah, woah!
冷静 伙计们 我们可是同一阵线的
Easy, guys. We're on the same team here.
多雷托先生
Mr. Toretto...
我是经由我们共同的朋友
I'm here on the recommendation...
介绍而来的
of a, mutual friend of ours.
-霍布斯先生 -你他妈到底是谁
- Mr. Hobbs? - Who the hell are you?
我 我就是个普通人
Me? I'm just a guy.
一个无名小卒
I'm, Mr. Nobody.
无名小卒的出场可真是盛大
That's a big entrance for a nobody.
那个把我们共同的朋友送进医院的家伙
And the guy who put our mutual friend in the hospital...
你刚刚让他逃走了
you just let him get away.
我刚刚是救了你一命吧 多姆
I think I might've just saved your ass there, Dom.
你能先放了我的人吗
Listen, you think you can let go of my guy there?
他被你勒得脸色发青了
He's beginning to turn a little blue.
非常感谢
I appreciate that.
他们来了
Here they come.
听着 多姆
Listen, Dom.
在黑暗世界和像我这样的幽灵之间有一场战争
There's a war going on between shadows and ghosts like me.
而你和你的团队
You and your team unwittingly
在伦敦无意间卷入了这场战争中
walked into the middle of it in London...
而且显然 它现在还缠上了你
and it appears it's now followed you home.
要怎么做 你随意
It's up to you.
我要去喝酒了
I'm gonna have a beer.
欢迎你一起来
You're welcome to join me.
顺便说一下 我可以帮你抓到戴克·肖
By the way, I can get you Deckard Shaw.
埃尔塞贡多作战基地 加利福尼亚
比利时麦芽酒
Belgian ale.
天啊 那些酿酒僧太厉害了
Man, those monks got it right.
我虽然不太了解禁欲之类的事情
I don't know about the whole celibacy thing,
但是一提到啤酒
but when it comes to beer...
你要来一杯吗
Would you like one?
我比较喜欢科罗娜[墨西哥啤酒]
I'm more of a Corona man myself.
你的档案 不仅详细
Your files, not only detailed...
而且非常有趣
It's, extremely entertaining.
肖的能力之强就好比他是个影子
Look, Shaw's power is that he's a shadow.
他非常擅长于出入各种地方
He's really good at getting in and out of places...
无声无息
without being seen and
除了留下个死尸以外 不会留下任何蛛丝马迹
leaving nothing but a body count in his wake.
他是个合法的英国混蛋
He's a legitimate English badass.
但老实告诉你 多姆
But to be honest with you Dom,
我对戴克·肖不屑一顾
I don't give two shits about Deckard Shaw.
我想要的是你
It's you I want.
因为你我联手可以得到我们彼此想要的东西
Because you and I can help each other get what we both need.
洗耳恭听
I'm listening.
就在最近 由被通缉的恐怖分子莫斯·杰坎德
Just recently, a private military company...
领导的一间私人军事公司
led by a wanted terrorist named Mose Jakande...
[姓名]   莫斯·杰坎德
绑架了一名黑客 只知道名字叫拉姆齐
kidnapped a hacker known only by the name "Ramsey".
虽然这如同大海捞针
Lady Liberty's got her panties
但我们一定要找到她
in a bunch over this but rightfully so...
因为这个拉姆齐发明了一个有趣的玩意儿
because this Ramsey has created something interesting.
-启动吧 -是 长官
- Bring it up. - Yes, sir.
跟“天眼”
Say hello...
打个招呼吧
To God's Eye.
这个小混蛋
Now this little bastard hacks
黑了数字网络里的所有东西
into anything that's on a digital network.
也就是说 黑了所有手机 卫星 自动提款机和电脑
That means every cellphone, satellite, ATM machine, and computer,
在同一时间
simultaneously.
只要你的设备有麦克风或者镜头
If it's got a microphone or a lens,
天眼就能通过它找到你
God's Eye can use it to find you.
所以你请我来就是让我看一个追踪装置
So you invited me here to show me a tracking device.
应该说 是批量追踪装置
On steroids. Lots of them.
我这么跟你说吧
Let me put it to you this way.
我们花了将近十年才找到本·拉登
It took us nearly a decade to find Osama bin Laden.
但有了这装备 我们在几小时之内就能
With this, we could locate him anywhere on the planet
在这个星球的任何地方找到他
in a couple of hours.
这是一个非常重要的装置
Now that's a serious piece of machinery...
一旦落入坏人手中就有可能导致大灾难
that could be catastrophic in the wrong hands.
但出于一些非常恶心的政治原因
But for some very nauseating, political reasons...
任何牵涉到美国政府或者军队的营救计划
any rescue plans involving any US government forces or entity...
都被严令禁止
has been strictly ruled out.
这就是我需要你的原因
And that's why I need you.
但我为什么需要你呢
But why do I need you?
我完全可以走出去 喝完剩下的科罗娜
I mean I could go back outside, enjoy the rest of the Coronas...
让肖自己来找我
let Shaw come to me.
你是可以那么做 但目前为止效果如何
You could do that. How's that working out for you so far?
你的朋友们 一个死了 一个躺在医院
You got one friend in the ground, another one in the hospital...
当然还有那个炸弹
and then of course there's that little issue of the bomb...
炸毁了你的家
that destroyed your home.
肖的世界是由不得你掌控的
Shaw lives in a world that doesn't play by your rules.
不管你喜不喜欢
Like it or not...
现在 你也在那个世界了
you live in that world now, too.
你想知道要怎么杀死影子吗
You wanna know how to kill a shadow?
只需要照一点光就可以了
You just shine a little light on it.
如果你帮我拿到天眼
If you get the God's Eye for me...
我已经为你申请到了使用许可
I've already got authorization
让你找到肖为止
for you to use it until you get Shaw.
这样你就从猎物变成了猎人
You go from the hunted, to the hunter.
在这个地球上 肖再也无处可藏
And there's no place on Earth Shaw can hide from you.
更重要的是
More importantly,
你跟你的家人
you and your family...
不用再参加任何葬礼了
don't go to any more funerals.
只要找到拉姆齐 你就能得到天眼
You get Ramsey, you get the God's Eye...
也就能找到肖了
You get Shaw.
一切就是这么水到渠成
Well that's the windup and the pitch.
现在我已经给你提供了
Now that I've given you this
如此有效且高度机密的信息
incredibly sensitive and highly classified information...
你有什么打算 多雷托
What do you think, Toretto?
我想你已经知道我会怎么做了
I think you already know what I'm gonna do.
很好
Good.
但是 我要用我的方式
But, it'll be my way.
还有我自己的人
And my crew.
我就知道你会这么说
I assumed you might say that.
所以我擅自集合了你的团队
Which is why I've taken the liberty of gathering your team.
太疯狂了
This is crazy.
这他妈到底是怎么回事
What the hell is going on in here?
我们的情报显示 拉姆齐会由
Our intelligence suggests that Ramsey will be transported...
一列武装车队护送 转移到高加索山脉
by an armed motorcade through the Caucasus mountain range.
如果他们扫清障碍 顺利到达目的地的话
If they clear this range and reach their destination...
我们就再找不到拉姆齐了
Ramsey's as good as gone.
让我捋一捋情况
So let me get this straight.
只有一条出入的路对吗
There's only one road that leads in or out...?
两面都是悬崖
Sheer drops on every side...
这该死的车队前后一英里各有
A motorcade from hell protected by a small army...
一小支武装部队保护着
from one mile on either direction?
嗯 差不多是这样
Yeah, that's about it.
-你说完了吗 -没 还没
- You done? - No, I'm not done.
先前你们让我闯进警察局 好吧我答应了
So you all wanted me to break into a police station, fine.
然后你们要我截停一辆坦克
Then you asked me to stop a tank.
我虽然心里不乐意 但我还是照做了
I wasn't happy about it, but I did it.
跟着你们又想出了一个绝顶好主意
Then you came up with this brillant idea...
要射下有史以来最大的飞机之一 行
to shoot down one of the largest airplanes, ever.
我就朝天射了两下 把那飞机打下来了
I shot that shit outta the sky...
那也没什么
It's nothing.
但是现在 朋友
But this right here, my friend...
这真的是我这辈子听过最蠢的主意
happens to be the stupidest idea I've ever heard of in my life.
我都忘了 你一个人就把那架飞机打了下来
I forgot that, you were the only one to bring that plane down.
不对 我见过他
No, only thing I've ever
唯一打倒过的就是无膝丹尼斯
seen him take down was "No knees" Denise.
记得吗 毕业舞会的时候
Remember? At prom?
不是吧 布莱恩 你真的要这样子吗
Really, Brian? You're gonna do that right here?
看吧 你们都在吐我槽
See, y'all try'na get me off my point.
我想说的是 我厌倦了由别人
All I'm saying is, I'm tired of everybody around me...
做决策
making all the decisions.
这一次 我来指挥
This time, I lead.
说真的 如果这次不让我做决策 我就不干
Seriously. If I don't start making decisions, I'm out.
好吧 罗曼
All right, Roman.
你有什么计划
What do you got?
我的意思是 我还没有
I mean, I wouldn't try to
准备好立刻接掌指挥棒
get into the whole leadership thing, like, now.
你们知道我在说什么吗 我只是在
You know what I'm saying? I'm just kind of...
在某种程度上想要做出决定
Talking about like, at some point.
好比说 当我们
Like, you know, when we...
随便了 我是说 我觉得
Whatever. I mean, I think...
我们从这里开始
Let's hit it from here.
-我不认为那是 -不 不要发表意见
- I don't think that that's... - No, don't think.
那是我的工作
That's my job.
好吧
Okay.
不可能从那里攻入的
It is impossible to hit it there.
那几乎是整座山最安全的地方
That is literally the most secure spot on the mountain.
为什么 因为你根本没法到那
Why? Because you cannot physically access it.
现在明白了吧 这就是这个地方那么棒的原因
Now see, that's what makes it so sweet.
因为他们根本不会想到
Because it's the place
我们会从这个地方攻入
that they least expect us to hit them from.
虽然不想承认 但他确实说到了点子上
As much as I hate to admit it, he's on to something there.
你觉得呢 多姆
What do you think, Dom?
这里吗
Here?
没错
Yeah.
我觉得我们有计划了
I think we got a plan.
思路完全错误
Completely wrong thinking.
但我喜欢
And I like it.
-瞧见了吧 -我很擅长这个
- You see? - I'm good at this.
擅长
Good?
好吧
Okay.
那你们打算怎么到这条路上
How are you planning on getting on that road?
这个么 泰吉
Well, Tej?
我觉得我倒真是有个计划了
I think I may actually have a plan for that.
看什么 我懂分权
What? I delegated.
这才是一个优秀的领导该做的
That's what good leaders do.
领导
Leader!
你知道 当我看到你的资料时
You know, when I was reading your files...
我对你带队获得的成果印象深刻
I was impressed with what you've accomplished with your team.
但是 现在见到了他们 我不得不说 多姆
But, meeting them now I gotta say, Dom...
你真的很有领导天赋
you truly have a gift.
把我的工作坊当做你们新的乐园吧
Consider my workshop your new playhouse.
我想你们会发现我们的车
I think you'll find our cars...
极其吸引人
extremely appealing.
还有你们的团队
And your team...
现在完整了
is now complete.
我去了房子那里
I went to the house.
到处找你
I was looking for you everywhere.
你快把我吓死了
You scared the shit outta me.
你永远不会孤单一人
You will never be alone...
你在哪找到这个的
Where did you find that?
在韩的车里
Found it in Han's car.
它是作为信息留下来的
It was left as a message.
意味着我要回来的信息
A message I plan on returning.
你可以吗
Can you ride?
行呀 我当然可以
Yeah, of course I can.
韩也是我的家人
Han was my family, too.
布莱恩
Brian!
我们需要给全部的车子装上长途悬架
We're gonna need long travel suspension...
和防滑差速器
limited slip differentials in all of them.
你还好吗
How you doing.
泰吉
Tej!
我要把这辆车和那辆车
I want the demon lovechild between that...
的优势结合起来
and that.
那可是很厚的装甲
That's a lot of armor.
重量增加会减慢你的速度
Just gonna add more weight, slow you down.
这次可不仅仅是要速度
This time it ain't just about being fast.
我没问题
Yeah, I'm good.
印象电影
SSK•FanSub
你们 你们知道我在说什么 对吧
From the streets, you know what I'm sayin'?
这没什么的
It's nothing.
印象电影 您的私人影院
嘿 罗曼 你已经吓尿了 是吗
Hey, Roman, you're freaking out, ain't you?
-没 -没错 你肯定吓尿了
- No. - Yeah, you are.
我说了 没有
I said, no.
听着伙计 成熟的男人敢于去直面自己的内心
Listen man, it takes a grown man to embrace his feelings.
你要是想哭 就哭吧
If you need to cry, just go ahead and cry.
作为你的朋友 你知道我十分关心你的健康
As your friend, you know I'm concerned about your well-being.
所以我提前
Which is why I took the precaution...
在你的储物柜里放了成人纸尿布
of putting some adult diapers in your glove compartment.
你就不能闭嘴吗 伙计
Can you just chill out, man?
虽然我以前也见识过一些大场面
I have seen some crazy shit,
多姆 但这一次可是牵涉重大
Dom, but this really could make some waves.
所以大家尽量低调点 好吗
So let's just try to keep it as low key as possible, huh?
我不一直都很低调吗
Don't I always?
我告诉你 如果
I tell you what: you knock
你这次真做成了
it down a couple of notches this time...
我就不喝比利时啤酒 改喝科罗娜
and I'll swap out my Belgian for a keg of Corona.
到时你可要喝个够
You'd be doing yourself a favor there.
有人能告诉我
Can somebody just walk me
现在到底是要干什么吗
through what we're supposed to be doing here?
行了 罗曼 这可是你的计划 你悠着点
Come on, Rom. This was your plan, you gotta embrace it.
不 这不是我的计划
No, this was not my plan.
好了 出发了 游戏开始了
Yeah, here we go. Gametime.
罗曼 你需要来点新鲜空气吗
Roman, you need some fresh air?
接下里就有大把新鲜空气了
'Cause you about to get a whole lot of it.
好了 开始了
Okay, here we go!
总是能刷新自己的极限 哈
Just when you didn't think it can get any better, huh?
啊 我操
Oh, shit!
这才是活着呢
Now we're moving.
大家都怎么样 都出来了吗
Everybody good? Everybody make it out?
你应该告诉他们 这不适合你
You should tell 'em, that this is not for you!
这不是你的任务
This is not your mission!
罗曼 怎么回事 伙计 给我回话 快呀
Rom, what's up man! Talk to me, come on!
-我做不到 -见鬼了你做不到
- I can't do it. - The hell, you can't!
快点 伙计 你就换个档
Come on man! You throw that
倒个车就行了 快从飞机上滚下来
thing in reverse and get your ass out here now!
我做不到 好吗 听到我说的话了吗
Look I can't do it, okay? Listen to what I'm saying.
现在可不是退缩的时候
Now isn't the time!
我要和飞行员一起留在飞机上
I'mma stay up here with the pilot.
我们会在上空盘旋
We're gonna circle around and
确保能够从空中控制车子降落
make sure we're holding them down from up here!
我们没时间了
We're running out of time!
降落伞有导航控制
The chute is guided by GPS!
你什么都不用做
You don't have to do anything!
-泰吉 -我准备好了
- Tej! - I'm already on it.
听着 伙计 听着
Listen, man. Listen
对不起让大家失望了
I'm sorry to let y'all down,
好吗 我就待这里了
okay? I'mma go ahead and stay up here.
不 兄弟
No, brother.
-我很抱歉让你失望了 -什么
- I'm sorry to let you down. - What?
这是不是
Is that...?
泰吉 你做了什么
Tej! What are you doing?
不
No!
泰吉
Tej!
我恨你 泰吉
I hate you, Tej!
准备好
Get ready!
马上就要着陆了
Ground's coming fast!
来吧 宝贝
C'mon, baby.
来吧
Come on.
安全着陆 宝贝儿
Touchdown, baby!
全员检查 所有人报数
Car check. Call it in.
-着陆 -着陆
- Check. - Check.
我没问题 开始吧
I'm good, let's do this.
哈喽 大家伙儿
Hello? Please man!
谁来帮帮我 有人吗
Get me outta here, somebody!
别 要撞树了
No! The trees!
我擦
Shit.
坐稳了 罗曼 我们一会儿回来接你
Sit tight, Roman. We'll come back for you.
计划可不是这样的
This is not the plan!
高加索山脉 阿塞拜疆
好了
All right.
阻截的机会只有一次 多姆
You got one chance to hit them here, Dom.
要是错过了 他们就会回到他们的大本营
You miss, they'll make it to their black site...
他们会不择手段地把他们需要的信息从拉姆齐口中榨出来
they'll squeeze whatever information they need out of Ramsey.
那个装置和你抓住肖的
The device and your chance
机会永远不会再有了
of ever getting Shaw will be gone for good.
这事不可能发生的
That ain't gonna happen.
咱们接应点见
I'll see you at the pickup.
拉姆齐 应该在那辆巴士里
Ramsey, will be in the bus.
那咱们开工吧
Then let's do this.
上尉我们有客人了 发现有四辆车
Captain we have company. Four cars inbound.
什么 不
What, no!
-泰吉 对准它 -我来了
- Tej, shoot it! - I'm on the way!
好了 保持队形
All right, formation!
这可是防弹的 宝贝儿
Bulletproof, baby.
撞它
Punch it!
爽呆了
Strike!
准备 发射
Guns, free.
是的 长官
Yes, sir.
别啊
No!
我操
Shit!
快躲开
Get out of the way!
这那是枪啊 他妈的根本就是炮
Those aren't guns, those are goddamn cannons!
肯定是反装甲配备
Armor piercing rounds!
钩住
Hook 'em up.
布莱恩 泰吉 爆破
Brian, Tej, blow it!
动手吧
Lock it up.
布莱恩 该你上了
Brian, you're up!
再近点 泰吉
Little closer, Tej!
拉姆齐
Ramsey?
别过来 退后
Stay away from me! Stay back!
别碰我
Don't you touch me!
我的名字叫布莱恩 我是来救你出去的
My name's Brian, and I'm gonna get you out of here...
但是我需要你保持冷静 好吗
but I'm gonna need you to settle down, all right?
我要把手上的东西解开
I'm gonna cut those things off of you.
长官
Sir?
长官 有一辆未知车辆正在接近中
Sir, we have an unidentified vehicle approaching.
快过来 近点
Come on! Closer!
你要跳下去
You have to jump!
我们没时间了 快来
We're out of time. Come on.
我们得离开这里
We gotta get out of here!
快跳
Come on!
看着我
Look at me!
如果你不跳 我们都会死在这里 明白吗
If you don't jump, we're gonna die! Okay?
你能做到的 来
You're jumping. Come on!
一
One.
二
Two!
喔 喔 喔
Well, well, well.
抓住我的手
Take my hand!
欢迎参加这场派对 肖先生
Welcome to the party, Mr. Shaw.
莱蒂 跟着布莱恩
Letty, stay with Brian.
靠
Oh shit!
你在干什么 你疯了吗
What are you doing? This is crazy!
让你保命
Keeping you alive!
前面是悬崖
There's a cliff.
悬崖 悬崖
Cliff! Cliff!
不要
No!
慢出翔
Too slow!
耶
Yeah!
我回来了 小婊子们
I'm back, bitches!
你没事吧
You good?
谢了
Thank you.
罗曼 和其他人会合
Roman! Get back to the others.
那你呢
What about you?
别担心我
Don't worry about me.
我不得不说 你真佩服你
I have to say, I am impressed.
我很想认识一下
I would very much like to know the name...
给我带来这么多麻烦的人
of the man who is causing me so much trouble.
那里已经没有退路了
There is no way out of there.
他在做什么
What is he doing?
他就像是被车头灯吓愣的鹿一样
He's frozen like a damn deer on headlights.
多雷托可不是鹿
Toretto ain't no deer.
做点什么 多米尼克
Come on, Dominic.
把那个女孩交给我们 我放你一条生路
Give us the girl, and I'll let you live.
你打算怎么办
What are you going to do?
你最好带上头盔
You might wanna put on your helmet for this one.
瞄准开车的
Target the driver!
靠 他到底在想什么
Dammit! What is he thinking?
你疯了
You're insane!
你方向搞错了
You're pointing the wrong way!
是吗
Am I now?
听我命令
Fire on my mark.
有意思
Interesting.
三
Three!
二
Two!
坐稳了
Hold on.
一
One!
开火
Fire!
看起来你又逃过一劫
Looks like our demon lovechild worked.
这也算是下山的一种方法
That's one way down a mountain.
拉姆齐在哪儿
Where's Ramsey?
小甜心醒了
Hello Kitty's awake.
我觉得她看着不像个黑客
She don't look like a hacker to me.
是吗 那黑客该是什么样子的
Oh yeah? And what do hackers look like?
至少不该
They don't suppose to look...
像那个样子
like that.
我只是说 比如
I'm just saying, like,
他们通常带着怪异的眼镜
how they normally wear them li'l weird glasses...
驼着背 还有
that's all crooked, with
因为喝多了苏打水长得满脸都是粉刺
pimples all over they face from drinking soda.
相信我 就这样的身材
I mean trust me, with a body like that...
完全不像是个搞电脑的
I ain't gonna park it behind a computer.
你感觉怎么样
How you feeling?
撞到头了吗
Did you hit your head?
反胃吗 有没有耳鸣
Feeling nauseous? Ears ringing?
没有吗
No?
我的另一只鞋呢
Where's my shoe?
你坠崖的时候它飞出去了
It flew off when you crashed.
你如果有
When you start experiencing
刚才我说的症状 告诉我 好吗
any of those things, let me know. Okay?
我不知道是该为救我一命而感谢你
I don't know whether to thank you for rescuing me...
还是该为把我扔出悬崖而打你一顿
or to kick your ass for throwing me off a cliff.
感谢我们还是打我们一顿二选一吗
Thank us or kick our ass, huh?
不如你告诉我们装置在哪儿
How about you tell us where that device is?
我把它寄给了一位朋友
I mailed it to a friend.
在阿布扎比
In Abu Dhabi.
这么容易就开口了
That was pretty easy.
刚才那队人可能会为了这个信息对你严刑拷打
That other team would've tortured you for that information.
我不信任他们
I didn't trust them.
我信任你们
I trust you.
你为什么相信我们 你又不认识我们
Now why would you trust us? You barely know us.
我了解得够多了
I know enough.
之前是警察 军人 或者类似那样的身份
Ex-cop. Military, something like that.
你打倒那些家伙的方式 一看就是经过训练的
The way you took out those guys, serious training.
你是高技术的 长着张黑客的脸
Tech guy. Offended by the hacker remark, naturally.
大哥
Alpha.
大嫂
Mrs. Alpha.
逗比
Joker.
错了
Wrong.
是另一个大哥
Double Alpha.
小甜心 你明白我的意思吗
Man-candy. Y'know what I'm saying?
伙计 你还是坐下吧
Man, sit your candy-ass down.
我感受到了你们深深的恶意
The disrespect is real around here.
生活是二进制的 不是零就是一
Life is binary. Zeroes and ones.
只有两种东西可以把一支团队凝聚在一起
Only two things keep a group like this together.
恐惧或者忠诚
Fear or loyalty.
而我在你们中间感受不到任何的恐惧
And I don't see a drop of fear among you guys.
分析得真到位 除了一件事
Very impressive. Just one thing.
他们没有结婚
They're not married.
她刚回来你就哪壶不开提哪壶
She's so off as crack, you're just gonna roll with it?
你还有脸告诉我一个团队里不能有两个大哥呢
You're telling me there can't be a double alpha in one group?
你们为美国政府工作吗
You work for the US government?
我们有共同的利益
We got similar interests.
泰吉 给他们回话
Tej, call it in.
我们要去中东
We're going to the Middle East!
嘿 多姆 山上那回真够拉风啊
Hey, Dom, it was pretty wild in that mountain, huh?
侥幸而已
That was too close.
但是至少任务完成了
But we got the job done.
你知道疯狂的是什么吗 是
Know what the crazy thing is? It's...
你喜欢那种枪林弹雨的感觉
You missed the bullets.
真是一团糟呀
That's messed up, huh?
布莱恩 我见过你从火车上 飞机上跳下来
Brian, I've seen you jump from trains, dive from planes.
遇见你的时候我就看到了你身上的勇气
Hell, I saw your courage the day I met you.
是么
Right.
你想知道我见你做过的最勇敢的事是什么吗
You wanna know the bravest thing I've ever saw you do?
就是成为米娅的好丈夫
Be a good man to Mia?
成为我外甥杰克的好父亲
Being a great father to my nephew, Jack.
每个人都在寻求刺激
Everyone's looking for their thrill...
但是真正存在的
but what's real,
是家人
is family.
你的家人
Your family.
牢记这一点 布莱恩
Hold on to that, Brian.
阿布扎比 阿拉伯联合酋长国
这可比我想的要热多了
This was hotter than I thought it would be.
对呀 我们在沙漠里 所以不热才鬼
Yeah, well, we are in the desert so, it would be hot.
不 我说的不是天气
No, I ain't talking about the weather.
我的老天啊
My, my, my.
如此尤物 才值得我为她从飞机上跳下去
Now that, is a woman that's worth falling out a plane for.
你省省吧 伙计 她归我了
Get outta there, man. I got dibs on that.
我先看上她的
You see me looking at that.
你刚刚用“归”这个字了
Did you just say "Dibs"?
你是小学生吗
What are you, in the fourth grade?
伙计 你能不能不找我的茬儿
Man, can you just get outta there?
这是自由的年代
It's a free market.
你在说什么鬼
What are you talking about?
-一边凉快去 -我乐意
- Get outta that. - Free.
那就猜拳决定吧
Rock, paper, scissors for it.
你俩是认真的吗
Are you guys for real right now?
看看你们两个人
Look at you.
因为这就能吵起来 眼神像跟踪狂一样
You both look whooped already. You got stalker eyes.
我曾试过去追拉姆齐 两年前的事儿了
I tried to call dibs on Ramsey. Two years ago.
结果是我蛋碎了一地
Her knee, my balls.
相信我 那样做你会后悔的
Trust me, you don't wanna do that.
嘿 拉姆齐
Hey! Ramsey!
你好啊 扎法尔
Hello, Zafar.
看来你又认识了新朋友
So you made some new friends.
对 这几个新朋友脾气不太好
Yeah, some short- tempered new friends.
寄给你的驱动装置我现在要用 你放在哪了
I need the speed drive I sent you. Where is it?
噢 太棒了 你一定会很高兴 我把它卖了
Oh good, you will be pleased to know. I sold it.
你把它卖了
You sold it?
你听到了吧
You hear that?
我当时让你妥善保管的
I asked you to take care of it.
你为什么要卖了它
Why on Earth would you sell it?
我们要把东西拿回来
We're gonna need it back.
这决不可能
Impossible.
扎法尔 我藏了一些东西在装置里 它很重要
Zafar, I stashed something inside it. It's important.
好吧
Okay.
好消息是 它现在很安全
Good news is it is safe.
那坏消息呢
And the bad news?
安全过头了
It is very safe.
把它卖给住在那里的约旦王子了
Sold it to a Jordanian prince living up there.
亿万富豪
Trust fund billionaire.
他说他的超跑需要这装置
Said he wanted it in his supercar.
看吧 这
Now see, this...
才是我最喜欢的 亿万富豪 拥有超跑
This I like. Billionaire, supercar.
超跑是怎么个“超”法儿
What makes it so, "super"?
最高时速达到242英里每小时
242 mile per hour, top speed.
而且还是防弹的
And, it's bulletproof.
难道只有我一个人听了觉得性奋么
Am I the only one arouse right now?
这就像是 你知道我的意思么
It's like, y'know what I'm sayin?
说了你们也不懂
Whatever.
车放哪里了
Where does he keep it?
在顶楼的豪华公寓
In his penthouse.
一号楼
Tower number one.
为什么他要把车放在自己的公寓里
Now why in the hell would he keep his car in his penthouse?
他是亿万富豪 我的朋友
He's a billionaire, my friend.
他想怎样就怎样
He can do whatever he wants.
明天刚好是夏至日
Now, tomorrow happens to be the longest day of the year.
王子想明天下午举办派对 庆祝一翻
Prince wants to celebrate it, host a party, tomorrow afternoon.
你能让我们混进去 对吧
So you can get us up there, right?
当然可以
Sure.
不过穿成这样可进不去
But not dressed like that.
怎么了
What?
我这样穿有问题吗
Something wrong?
问题多了去了
There's a billion things wrong.
但不是现在
But not in this moment.
你看起来帅呆了
You look handsome.
我觉得不太自在
I feel awkward.
我也一样
You and me both.
看你穿成这样
Seeing you dressed like this...
让我想起了一些事
Just reminds me of something.
什么事
Of what?
旧时光
Old times.
你没事吧
You okay?
嗯 没事
Yeah, I'm fine .
登场了
Showtime.
不 听我说 伙计
No, listen, man.
他们告诉我这里每天都有这样的派对
They're telling me they party like this everyday,
这样盛大的派对每天都有啊
on this level, they party everyday.
真是太疯狂了 我想搬来这里住
This is crazy. I might have to move out here.
我想我可以创造一种新文化 那就是“黑拉伯人”
I think I'mma start a new culture. It's called "Blarab".
你懂的 就是阿拉伯黑人
You know, like Black Arab?
现在情况如何 泰吉
How are we looking, Tej?
我们马上就位
We're almost in position.
好 接下来我们这么做
Okay, so this is how we work this.
如果想要达到目的我们就必须保持同步
We gotta move in sync if we're gonna pull this off so let's...
再确认一遍 确保每个人都知道自己该做什么
go over it to make sure everyone clearly understands their role.
罗曼 说的就是你
Roman, that means you.
知道么 泰吉 你这样真的一点都不专业
You know what? You're being real unprofessional right now, Tej.
天眼的芯片就藏在
The God's Eye chip is hidden
王子超跑驱动装置里
in a speed drive installed in the prince's car...
他把车放在了保险库里
which he keeps in a safe room vault.
我看到了8至10名的安保人员严密戒备
Now I make 8 to 10 playing closed security.
更不要说王子
Not to mention the prince...
还有他的私人保镖了
and his personal bodyguards.
北面墙上有一排摄像头
Security cameras are clustered by the north wall
保险库就在那里
that's where the vault is.
要进入保险库
Now to get in that vault,
我们得黑进安保系统
we gotta tap into the security system...
只有通过王子的卧室才能接入
which can be accessed in the prince's bedroom.
好了 各位 我这就去
Alright, guys. I'm going in.
不好意思
Excuse me.
我在找
I was just looking for...
-派对在那里举行 -什么
- The party is that way. - What?
这房间不允许
This room is off...
一旦我们进入系统
Now once we're tapped in
拉姆齐和我就能黑入网络 把门打开
Ramsey and I can hack into the network and pop the door
这样你们就能进去 拿到芯片
so you can get in and get that chip.
等等 你漏了一步
Wait, wait. You missed a step.
你漏了我的部分 我该做什么
What about my steps? What am I supposed to be doing?
不 没有遗漏
No, we didn't miss anything.
你是最特别的存在 等我们需要你的时候
You're special team, so when we need you...
好好表现就是了
do what you do best.
他要表现什么
And that is?
发散光热 这只有罗曼·皮尔斯才做得到
Shine brightly, like only Roman Pearce can do.
你总算说了句人话
Now we're talking.
好了 泰吉 我进到房间了
Alright, Tej. I'm in.
找到电话插孔 接头一般都在那里
Find a phone jack. The tap always runs behind that.
你会看到一条350兆赫兹的电缆
It's gonna be a 350 mega Hertz CAT5 D cable.
那里可能还有几十条其他的电缆
They probably got a couple dozen back there.
不过你要找的是那对耦合电缆 上面做了充气增压处理
But this'll be the bonded pair with a plenum coat.
说人话 泰吉
English, Tej.
橘黄色的线就是了
It'll be the orange wire.
好了 女士们先生们 一切准备就绪
Alright, ladies and gentlemen, we are in the pilot's seat.
安保系统已覆盖
罗曼
Alright, Roman.
尽情绽放吧
Do whatever it is you do.
今天是你的生日吧 对吗
It's your birthday, right?
你是贾斯敏吗
Are you Jasmine?
天呐 别用生日的梗
God, no. Not the birthday routine.
生日快乐 这边请
Happy birthday to you. This way.
不好意思 真抱歉 借过一下 抱歉
Excuse me, so sorry. I'm coming through, sorry.
这边请
Right this way.
请容我使用一下下
Listen, excuse me one second.
伙计 你不能这样
Man, you ain't...
先生 太谢谢你了
Sir, thank you so much.
在场的各位 请大家聚到这边来
Listen, people. Please everybody, gather around.
听懂英语的就动起来
Understand something right now.
大家请听我说两句
Listen to what I'm telling y'all.
我们在此庆祝贾斯敏小姐的十八岁生日
We are here to celebrate Jasmine's 18th birthday.
生日快乐 亲爱的
Happy birthday, my dear.
祝你生日快乐
Happy birthday to you.
To you.
祝你生日快乐
真希望我没目睹这一惨况
I wish I didn't see that.
拉姆齐 把门打开
Ramsey, open it up for us.
收到
Copy that.
可以进去了
You're in.
知道这什么车吗
You realize what this is?
莱肯限量超跑
Lykan HyperSport.
市场价340万美金 起步到时速100公里不超过3秒
$3.4 million. 0 to 60 in less than 30 seconds.
全世界只有七辆
There's 7 of these things in the
而这家伙却把这辆车锁在保险库里
world and this guy keeps it locked up in a vault.
把如此野兽关在这样的笼子里 真是可悲
Nothing's sadder than locking a beast in a cage.
我现在真想朝那家伙脸上来一拳
Right now I really wanna punch him in the face.
好了
Okay.
开始干活吧
Let's get to work.
你坚持得住 对吧
You got this, right?
动作快点
Go.
好吧
All right.
你相信他是被我迷倒的吗
Would you believe I knocked him out with my charm?
你没那魅力 贱人
You ain't that charming, bitch.
有人入侵
封锁现场
不
No!
泰吉 我们要失败了 系统不受控制了
Tej, our magic trick is failing. We're losing systems.
我知道
I know.
找到了
I see it.
泰吉 现在情况怎么样
Tej, talk to me.
我正在努力 不过他们的安保系统把我踢出来了
I'm trying but their security system is locking us out.
听着 女士们先生们
Listen, ladies and gentlemen...
噢 他来了 这些都是你的伴舞吗
Oh, there he is. These your dancers?
这可是一场派对啊
This is a party, baby!
可能在座的一些嘉宾进入洗手间时
Some of ya'll probably went to the bathroom
发现所有的发胶都不见了
and noticed that all the hairspray was missing.
没错 就是她干的
Yep. She did it.
感谢你的配合
Thank you.
我们非常感谢您的光临
And we're so happy for you to be here.
看来你裙子下面别有一番天地
You look like you got some missiles underneath that dress.
他刚才该不会
He did not just...
你真这么说了吗
Did you just say that?
靠 别关门啊
Shit! Not the gate!
布莱恩 动作快点
Brian, faster!
我们会想尽办法争取时间的
We're playing all the defense we can up here.
但情势就要失控了 你们动作快一些
But we're gonna lose, you gotta hurry up.
谢天谢地 你来了
Thank god, you showed up.
这派对简直无聊死了
These parties bore me to death.
伙计们 快撤离那里
Guys get out of there right now.
有一队人马向你们那边去了
You've got an army headed your way.
布莱恩 快出来 别管芯片了
Brian, get up! Forget it!
泰吉 我们要开走这辆车
Tej, we're taking the car.
我就是干这一行的 你们都懂我的意思吗
This is what I do. Y'know what I'm sayin'?
莱蒂 莱蒂 你怎么样
Letty, Letty, talk to me.
你还好吗
Are you okay?
伙计们我顶不住了 最后一道门就要关上了
Guys I can't hold it. I'm losing the final gate.
你们得赶紧离开这里
You gotta get out of there.
把面板砸了
Tear off the dash!
仔细找找
Go through it.
等下 老兄 有话好好说
Wait, just hold on man.
该把这头野兽放出去了
Time to unleash the beast.
快走
Go!
跟我走 有我在
Stay with me, I got you.
我们赶紧离开这里
Let's get the hell outta here.
多姆 车可不会飞
Dom. Cars don't fly!
车不会飞
Cars don't fly!
我靠
Shit!
刹车坏了
No brakes!
什么
What?
-刹车坏了 -该死
- No brakes! - Shit!
不
No!
-拿到了 -快跳出去
- Got it! - Get out!
艾提哈德塔  阿布扎比 ↘
还想念枪林弹雨的日子吗 布莱恩
Still miss the bullets, Brian?
灾星们来了
There they are, disaster.
抱歉弄成这样
I'm sorry.
我把你们弄进阿布扎比最豪华的派对
I get you an invite to the most exclusive party in Abu Dhabi.
扎法尔
Zafar.
别来这套 你们偷了王子的车
No, no, you steal the host's car.
还飞穿了两栋大楼
And you jump it between two buildings.
实际上 是三栋大楼
Actually, it was three buildings.
噢 两栋 侮辱你们了 三栋 太了不起了 我的错
Oh! Two, insult. Three, honor. My bad
哇 哇 哇
Wow, wow, wow.
我得说
I have to say...
你们对低调
You've got an interesting
真是做了一次有趣的诠释 多雷托先生
interpretation there of low key, Mr. Toretto.
我以为我们已经达成了共识
I thought we had an understanding.
有时你手里拿到什么牌 就得出什么牌
Sometimes you have to play the hand you're dealt.
所以我才想当发牌的人
That's why I prefer to be the dealer.
晚安了
Good night.
把我从我的车库赶出去
Kicked out of my own garage.
好极了
This is great.
能让我看看吗
May I?
布莱恩
Brian.
把芯片给他
Give it to him.
就是这么一小块东西 闹出这么大的动静
All that trouble for this little.... thing.
恕我直言 多姆
With all due respect, Dom...
你真是完成得太出色了 你们所有人都是
You really did great work back there. All of you.
现在我手下所有人员待命
All of my men are now standing by...
全都听由你们差遣
and are fully at your disposal.
你来发令
Your call.
拉姆齐
Ramsey.
启动天眼 找到肖
Fire it up, and find me Shaw.
靠 这太疯狂了
Damn, this is crazy.
多谢
Thank you.
稍等下
Give me a second.
现在在做什么
What is it doing now?
狩猎
It's hunting.
现在我正黑入艾提哈德塔里的安保系统
Hacking into the security cameras at Ethihad Towers.
我们从最后一次看见肖的位置开始搜索
That's the last place we saw Shaw so that's where we start.
就是他 在那儿
That's him, right there.
等下 这上面的数字都是什么
Wait. What are these numbers out here for?
肖面部的生物识别码
It's biomapping Shaw's face.
这里所有的监控
It will run that against every camera...
所有的音频设备都会按照这个进行识别
Every audio device in this hemisphere.
找到了 看来他藏在这里
Bingo. Looks like he's holed up here.
绝佳的地点
That's perfect.
在自动化工厂 杳无人迹 可以躲藏的地点太多了
Automated factory, no people. Lots of places to hide.
你刚刚改写了追捕用时的新纪录
You just changed the face of manhunts forever.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我能查下我的邮件吗 很快的
Can I check my e-mail real quick?
两小时后就天亮了
Dawn's up in two hours.
届时我们将抓到肖
We're gonna go take down Shaw then.
收拾下准备行动
Go get changed.
我们现在就出发
We should go now.
你 还有你的手下 加上我
Just you, your team and me.
你不是说天亮后行动吗
I thought you said at dawn?
我的伙计们是世界上
My guys are racers.
最好的赛车手
Best drivers in the world.
但他们不是杀手
But they ain't killers.
跟你说了他会这么说的
Told you he'd say that.
我太了解你了 多姆 我和你一起去
I know you too well, Dom, and I'm going with you.
看来要来一次刺激的追捕行动了
Looks like we got a nice little hunting party.
把肖绳之于法吧
Let's go bag a shadow.
还有十公里 伙计们 准备大干一场吧
Ten clicks out, boys. Get ready to rock and roll.
目标抵达 武器预备准备好
Here we go. Weapons hot.
准备好了吗
You ready for this?
当然了
Yeah.
最后一餐希望你吃得开心
I hope you're enjoying your last meal.
就这点儿人吗
This is it?
你们就带这么多人吗
This is all you want?
十几个
A dozen men?
这些人对付你绰绰有余
I think you'll find it's more than enough.
我已经做了最坏的打算
I'm ready to meet my maker.
你呢
Are you?
你在期待什么 多雷托 趁我不备把我拿下
What were you expecting, Toretto? Catch me off guard?
还是要我站在这里 缴械投降
Me standing here, waving a white flag?
有没有听过这么一句话
Have you ever heard the saying:
敌人的敌人
"The enemy of my enemy...
就是朋友
is my friend?"
我没有朋友
I don't have friends.
我只有家人
I got family.
我可是有很多朋友
Well, I got a lot of friends.
保持阵型 谢普特
Keep your formation! Sheppard, clear one!
布莱恩 别管它了
Brian, leave it!
趴下
Get down!
我来背你
I got you.
天眼
The God's Eye.
你不会以为我就那么赤膊上阵吧
You didn't really think I was gonna walk in there naked, did you?
你伤得不轻
You got hit bad.
听着 多雷托
Look. Toretto.
我知道你不会听我的
I know you won't listen to me.
你也不会想听我接下来要说的话
You're not gonna wanna hear what I have to say.
但事实就是
But the truth is...
你必须要
you really ought to...
尝尝比利时啤酒 伙计
try that Belgian ale, man.
味道真的很独特
It's something special.
比利时啤酒是吗
Belgian ale, huh?
我们得送你去医院
We gotta get you to a hospital.
不 不用
No, you're not.
我随身带着我的医疗保险
I carry my own health insurance.
特种作战部队的急救人员马上就到
SOCOM Medics on standby. They're already inbound.
靠边停 孩子
Pull over, kid.
多姆 你一定要保护好拉姆齐
Dom, you got to protect Ramsey.
只要她活着
As long as she's alive,
就能用天眼锁定敌人 而他们心里也清楚
she can lock them out of God's Eye and they know that.
这就意味着 不找到她 他们是不会善罢甘休的
That means, they're not gonna stop coming until they've got her.
而当他们找到你们的时候
And this time when they come...
他们会不惜一切代价的
They're gonna come with everything they've got.
我不会丢下你的
I'm not leaving you.
你没有
You're not.
是我要丢下你们
I'm leaving you.
快走吧 多姆
Go now, Dom.
不管我们喜不喜欢 一场大战就要来了
A war is coming to us whether we like it or not.
大战一旦到来
But if a war's coming...
街道就是我们最得心应手的战场
We're gonna face them on the streets we know best.
我全力支持 但这太疯狂了
I'm all for winging it, but this is crazy, man.
那些雇佣兵来势凶猛
We got mercenaries with some real heat on us.
我不是在害怕 只是
I mean I ain't scared of nothing but...
我连把枪都没有
..I don't even have a gun.
还要枪
Gun?
我们拥有整座城市
We got a whole city.
而且还不止这些
And we may have more than that.
如果他们启用天眼
If they use God's Eye...
它就会利用镜头找到我们的位置
it will tap the cameras around to find our location.
这样我们就可以植入病毒
Which means we could plant a virus.
他们一旦接入我们就能黑进去
And then break in when they access it.
你是在说要攻击我的黑客设备
So you're talking about hacking my hacking device.
真聪明
That's brilliant.
是啊 但还有个问题
Yeah, but there's one problem.
就是信号的强度
The signal strength.
他们要在两英里范围之内
We can't start a hack on
我们才能开始攻击他们的系统
them until they're within a two mile range.
-那距离很近啊 -近
- That's really close. - Close?
那些人都是军人
These guys are military.
如果他们在两英里之内 我们早就死定了
If they're within two miles of us, we already dead.
我不知道你们怎么想
I don't know about y'all,
但我可不打算今天就死
but I didn't really plan on dying today.
活命的话只有一个方法
Only one way to stay alive.
我们拿拉姆齐当诱饵
We play keepaway with Ramsey.
什么
What?
我们一直移动的话他们就攻击不了我们
They can't hit us if we keep moving.
我来对付肖
And I'll take Shaw.
这么说
So basically we're just
我们是在玩声东击西 对吧
gearing up for a big game of hot potato, huh?
为什么我预感到我们不会再见面了呢
Why does it feel like I'm not gonna see you again?
我会回来取这个的
I'll come back for that.
你保证吗
Promise?
一言为定
Promise.
布莱恩 你没事吧
Brian, are you okay?
米娅 听我说
Mia? Listen to me.
一场大战即将来临
Something's about to go down.
如果二十四小时后没有我的消息
If you don't hear from me in 24 hours...
我要你带着杰克 好好生活下去
I need you to take Jack and move on.
明白吗
You understand?
你知道我在说什么吗
You understand what I'm saying?
不 我做不到 布莱恩
No I can't do that, Brian.
我做不到
No, I can't.
我们就要有第二个孩子了
We're gonna have another baby.
是个小女孩
It's a little girl.
她需要父亲
And she's going to need her father.
所以你要完成任务
So you have to finish what you're doing...
要回家 回到她身边
and you have to come home to her.
为了我们 你一定要回来
You have to come home to us.
抱歉我之前没有告诉你
I'm sorry I didn't tell you before.
我害怕你对家庭生活感到失望
I was scared you'd be disappointed with domestic life.
你知道 我这辈子做过
You know the best decision
最正确的决定就是走进那家店
I ever made was stepping into that store...
买了第一份三明治
buying that first sandwich.
那个三明治真的很难吃
It was such a bad sandwich.
我知道
I know.
但我还是吃了很多份
But I ate a lot of 'em.
我爱你 米娅
I love you, Mia?
别这么说
Don't do that.
怎么了
What?
你说得好像是在告别
The way you said it. It's like goodbye.
说点其他的
Say something else.
好吧 帮我亲亲杰克
Okay. Kiss Jack for me.
我会的
I will.
我爱你 布莱恩
I love you, Brian.
我爱你 米娅
I love you, Mia?
最后一程了
One last ride.
启动天眼 找到他们
Boot up God's Eye, and find them.
找到了
I'm getting something.
找到一个匹配信息 是多雷托
I got a positive ID. It's Toretto.
天眼定位在比佛利山庄和第七大道交界处
God's Eye is placing him at Hill and Seventh.
要跟着他吗
Should we follow him?
不用 让肖对付他
No. Let Shaw take care of him.
继续找拉姆齐
Find Ramsey.
遵命
Yes, sir.
我不知道为嘛我们要这样到处晃
I don't know why we gotta keep driving around like this.
就不能找个地方等着吗
Why can't we just pull over somewhere...
找个地下室什么的去理下思路
park, gather our thoughts in like a bunker somewhere?
因为这次不一样了
Because it does not work like that.
我们要和敌人保持最近的距离
We gotta stick close enough to the bad guys...
好让拉姆齐黑进去
in order to get in range for Ramsey to hack 'em...
但我们要保持移动
but we gotta be mobile
才不会轻易被干掉
enough not to get shot like fish in a barrel.
所以拜托你 打起十二分精神
So do me a favor, focus on the mission,
别让我们都被干掉
keep us from getting killed.
找到了 目标锁定
Got them. Target acquired.
她在一辆蓝色GTR的副驾驶座上
She's riding shotgun in a blue GT-R.
伙计们 他们来了
Guys, they're here.
有多少辆车
How many cars?
没有车
None.
没有车才是问题
And that's kind of the problem.
带他们转转
Let's give them a tour.
听我口令分开
Break on my mark.
三 二 一
Three, two, one.
行动
Go!
分开走没用的
Splitting up won't work.
你们是躲不过天眼的
You can't hide from God's Eye.
进入信号范围之内
In range.
拉姆齐 开始攻击
Ramsey, start the hack.
启动中
Initiating.
开始
Now.
启动中
老大 有人想要攻击系统
Sir, I think someone's trying to hack the system.
是拉姆齐
It's Ramsey.
出动猎食者无人机
Send in the predator!
把她干掉
Take her out!
猎食者已出动
Releasing predator.
我们好像甩掉直升机了
I think we lost the chopper.
但我想我们有个更大的麻烦
I think we got bigger problems than that!
噢 天呐
Oh, my God.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
老把戏
Going old school!
目标消失
它又追上来了
It's coming back around!
猎食者已重新锁定他们
The predator's back on 'em.
准备发射导弹
Ready missiles!
收到
Roger that.
发射
Fire!
该死
Shit!
我需要转移
I need a lateral.
罗曼 你在哪儿
Rom, where are you?
正往回赶 马上就到
Running back! Charging in.
在第三大道和春泉大道交叉口会合
Meet me on Third and Spring.
收到
You got it!
还剩一半了
I'm halfway there.
拿着电脑从窗户爬出去
Grab your computer and get in the window!
-为什么 -照做 快
- Why? - Do it, now!
快走 就现在
You gotta go! Right now!
发射
Fire!
不
No!
他没事
He made it!
真不敢相信我们做到了
Can't believe we pullled that off!
上传中
等等 我们还在遭受攻击
Wait, we're still being hacked.
什么
What?
天眼还能追踪到拉姆齐
God's Eye is still tracking Ramsey.
让无人机继续追踪她
Keep the drone in pursuit of her.
信号肯定是从某处发出来的
The signal has to be coming from somewhere.
洛杉矶晚间实况新闻
Breaking news out of Los Angeles tonight.
在一场飙车大战中
In what can only be described as vehicular warfare,
新闻快报
高速飙车
洛杉矶市中心
警察正在全速追击
police are engaged in a high speed pursuit...
我找到了 攻击信号
I got it. The piggyback in
是从那座卫星塔发出来的
the hack off that satellite tower right there.
毁了它
Take it out!
多雷托
Toretto.
等等 怎么了 都快好了啊
Wait, what happened? We were almost there.
信号丢失
他们切断了信号 我不能完成攻击了
They've cut the signal. I can't finish the hack.
什么意思
What do you mean?
布莱恩 他们把塔给炸了
Brian, they took out the tower!
爸爸 怎么了
Dad, what's going on?
爸爸要去工作了
Daddy's gotta go to work.
好了 宝贝女儿
Alright, baby girl.
埃琳娜马上就回来了
Elena's gonna be here in a little bit.
还是老规矩
You know our drill.
击三下祝我好运
Give me three for the road.
你以为这是街头斗殴吗
You thought this was gonna be a street fight?
还真他妈被你猜中了
You're goddamn right it is.
肯定有其他办法的
There has to be another way.
等等 我看到第六大道附近
Wait. I'm seeing half a
有几个信号塔
dozen cell towers between Sixth and State.
布莱恩 如果你能到
Brian, if you can get to the
其中一栋大楼顶端
top of any one of those buildings around there...
我们就可以把信号重新接上了
we can reroute the signal manually and finish the job.
这就去
I'm on it.
老大 你听到了吗
Sir, did you hear that?
奥康纳正朝信号塔跑去
O'Conner is on foot heading for a repeater.
他要重启攻击
He's gonna try to reinitiate the hack.
让无人机跟紧拉姆齐
Keep the drone on the girl.
吉特
Kiet.
奥康纳正赶往第六大道附近
O'Conner's on foot somewhere between Sixth and State.
不要让他靠近那里
Don't let him make it there.
警察在追我们
Boys is on us!
警察应付不了这些的
And them boys ain't ready for this!
卧槽
Shit!
一开始是坦克 然后是飞机
First a tank, then a plane...
现在连宇宙飞船都来了
Now we got a spaceship?
那不是宇宙飞船 那是无人机
That's not a spaceship, that's a drone!
噢 无人机吗
Oh it's a drone?
这会儿你开始挑我语病 就你发音标准
Now you gonna break it down and be articulate...
好像你知道这他妈到底怎么回事一样
like you already know what the hell is going on?
闭上你的臭嘴 好好开车
Shut your ass up and drive the car!
莱蒂 我们遇上麻烦了
Letty, the football's on fire!
我们需要支援
We need help!
坚持住 我就来了
Hang on! I'm coming!
拉姆齐 准备再来一次
Ramsey, get ready to go again.
无人机导弹已经锁定
Drone has missile lock.
发射
Fire!
目标已摧毁
Target destroyed.
等等 天眼还是能追踪到她
Wait! God's Eye still has her.
怎么可能
How can that be?
快起来
Get up. Come on.
快走 动作快
Let's go! Let's go.
他们在桥下换车了
They switched her under the bridge.
什么
What?
快离开这里
You gotta get outta here,
它跟着你 速度很快
it's on your trail and it's coming fast.
收到
Got it.
这车完了的话 谁来救我们
So if this car goes south, who's coming to save us?
谁来救我们 我们自救吧
Save us, honey? We're it.
他们在哪里
Where are they now?
向东六条街 开得很快
Six blocks east, hauling ass.
我要往哪里走 泰吉
Where we heading, Tej?
过了维修区有个服务电梯
There's a service elevator past the maintenance center.
那里直接通往信号塔
It will take you directly up to the repeater.
布莱恩 你得快点
Brian, you gotta hurry!
太慢了
Too slow!
它又追上来了
It's coming back.
在隧道里甩掉它
We'll lose them in the tunnel.
锁定
Got it!
发射
Fire!
我甩不掉这个东西
I can't shake this thing!
猎食者导弹锁定
The predator has missile lock.
干掉他们
Take it out!
天呐
No way.
等等 怎么回事
Wait! What happened?
老大 有人毁了我们的无人机
Sir, someone just double tapped our drone.
什么
What?
嘿 你带了装甲部队来吗
Hey, did you bring the cavalry?
妹子 我就是装甲部队
Woman, I am the cavalry.
谁说不是呢
Of course you are.
那是谁啊
Who is that?
那是霍布斯
That's Hobbs!
我到信号塔了
I'm at the repeater.
接入线缆在下面
The access cable's in the base.
插到你手机上拉姆齐就能重新连上
Just plug it into your phone and Ramsey will be back online.
拉姆齐 开始吧
Ramsey, go!
布莱恩成功了 我们重新连上了
Brian did it. We're back in.
覆盖成功
我们拿回天眼了
We've got God's Eye back.
-我们失去天眼了 -什么
- We lost the God's Eye! - What?
靠
Shit!
军方出动了 三分钟内到达
Military's inbound. Three minutes and closing.
我们要马上撤离
We need to get the hell outta here.
泰吉 罗曼 我这就来
Tej, Roman, I'm on my way.
收到了 兄弟 一会儿见
Alright, homie. I'll see you there.
我看见多雷托了
I have eyes on Toretto.
肖也在
Shaw's in the way.
看来我们的友情到此结束了
Then it seems our friendship is at an end.
动手吧
Do it.
街头斗殴的重点就是
The thing about street fights?
赢的永远是街道
The street always wins.
再见了 多雷托
Goodbye, Toretto.
干掉他
Take him out!
王八
Son of a...
我需要帮助
I need some help out here!
我们被击中了
We're getting killed.
快来帮忙
I need some backup!
不 你这个王八蛋
No! Son of a bitch.
他逃跑了
He's getting away!
不 快阻止他
No, stop them.
不能失手
Don't miss.
多姆
Dom!
挺住
Come on.
坚持住
C'mon, buddy.
他还活着吗
Is he breathing?
按照我说的做 把他的头侧向一边
Here's what I need you to do. Keep his head tilted up.
好的 让他的背部保持这样
All right. Keep it back like this.
捏住他的鼻子 让他头侧向一边 开始人工呼吸 快
Clinch his nose, keep his head tilted. Breathe in him now. Go.
很好
That's good.
醒醒 多姆
Come on, Dom.
快醒来 妈的
Come on, goddammit!
快醒过来啊
You come on, you breathe!
快快 呼吸啊
Go, go, breathe!
快 继续人工呼吸 多姆 你倒是呼吸啊
C'mon, dammit. Let's go. Come on, Dom! I need you to breathe.
醒醒 多姆 快醒过来
Come on, Dom. Come back, c'mon.
加把劲 兄弟 多姆 醒醒
Come on, buddy. Dom, come on!
让开
Back off!
你别哭了 快给他人工呼吸
Will you stop? Breathe into him.
做人工呼吸啊
You breathe into him.
-给他做人工呼吸 -你走开
- You breathe into him. - Back off!
求你了 多姆
Please, please, Dom.
多姆 宝贝
Dom, baby.
我知道你现在很难受
I know you're hurting right now.
但我要你仔细听我说
But I want you to listen.
醒过来 好好看着我
Stay awake and focus on me.
我都记起来了
I remember everything.
记忆像洪水一样涌了回来
It came to me like a flood.
就是那晚 在多米尼加共和国
That night, in the Dominican Republic.
我们结婚的那晚
The night we got married.
戒指准备了吗
这个能代替吗
Will this do?
这一刻就是我们的永远
We have eternity in this moment.
你不会再孤单一人了
You will never be alone again.
我发誓 无论你去哪里 我就去哪里
I vow, wherever you go, I go.
你飙车 我就飙车
You ride, I ride.
你战斗 我就战斗
You fight, I fight.
如果你敢死在我面前 多米尼克·多雷托
And if you ever die on me, Dominic Toretto...
我也会跟着你去死
I'm gonna die with you.
我爱你 莱蒂
I love you, Letty.
永远爱你
I will always love you.
你死 我也死
If you die, I die.
可是我还没有准备好离开这个世界
And I'm not ready to leave this place yet.
这一时刻 还是属于我们的
This moment, still ours.
所有的事我都记起来了
I remember everything.
全部都记得了
I remember it all.
也该记起来了
It's about time.
哦 天啊
Oh, God.
你为什么不告诉我们结婚了
Why didn't you tell me we were married?
我总不能告诉你 你是爱我的
Because you can't tell someone they love you.
我的天啊
Holy shit.
中央情报局秘密监狱
你确定你带够人手了吗 霍布斯
You sure you brought enough backup with you, Hobbs?
哦 这些不是来保护我的
Oh, they ain't mine.
他们是来保护你的
They're here to protect you.
以防我一不小心杀了你
From me killing your ass.
你知道这里是关不住我的 对吧
You do know, none of this will keep me, right?
等你掘地38英尺 挖穿这钢筋混凝土
Well I want you to dig through 38 feet of concrete and steel...
还有我的拳头和裹尸袋
and my fist and a bodybag
在等着你
will be waiting for you on the other side.
所以我建议你现在就开始挖吧
So I suggest you get to digging, boy.
-孩子他爸 过来玩啊 -来了
- Daddy, come play. - Yeah.
看看他 快看他在那儿
Look at him, look at him.
你好重啊 哥们
Yeah, buddy.
-使命召唤 -没错
- Duty calls. - It does.
-快来啊 -咱们去找妈妈
- Come on... - Let's get momma...
你知道吗 我们被晒黑
Y'know we gotta tan because...
是因为太阳
the sun is out, you know...
只有三成热 但我能晒成
medium rare, but I can get like...
非常完美的全黑
well done, like really dark.
-你戳我做什么 -你少说两句
- What you nudging me for? - Close your mouth for two seconds.
多看两眼吧 伙计
Just open your eyes, man.
如画一般美
Beautiful.
这才是他真正的归属
That's where he belongs.
家
Home.
这一直都是他的归属
Where he's always belonged.
一切都时过境迁了
Things are gonna be different now.
你真棒
You got it. What...
再来一次
One more time.
不说再见就走了吗
You aren't going to say goodbye?
耶 干得漂亮
Yeah! Good job!
不愧是我儿子
My man.
永远不会再见
It's never goodbye.
See You Again by: Wiz Khalifa
It's been a long day without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
We've come a long way from where we began
Oh, I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
When I see you again
First you both go out your way
And the vibe is feeling strong
And what's small turn to a friendship
A friendship turn into a bond
And that bond will never be broken
And the love will never get lost
And when brotherhood come first
Then the line will never be crossed
Established it on our own
When that line had to be drawn
And that line is what we reach
So remember me when I'm gone
It's been a long day
Without you, my friend
And I'll tell you all about it when I see you again
When I see you again
嘿 不说再见你就想走了吗
Hey, thought you could leave without saying goodbye?
我总说我的生活就是四分之一英里的极速竞赛
I used to say I lived my life a quarter mile at a time.
我想这就是我们成为兄弟的原因
And I think that's why we were brothers.
因为你也一样
Because you did, too.
-这就是你的车 -我的车
- This is your car. - My car?
你们都自由了
You're all free.
有家的感觉啊
Home, sweet home.
-近来可好 兄弟 -谢谢邀请我来参赛
- What's happening, boy? - Thanks for the invite.
想去兜一圈吗
Wanna go for a drive?
无论你身在何方
No matter where you are,
在四分之一英里以外的赛道
whether it's a quarter mile away,
还是在遥远世界的另一边
or halfway across the world...
人生中最重要的
The most important thing in
永远都是这屋檐下的你们
life will always be the people in this room.
此时 此刻
Right here, right now.
敬这个大家庭
Salud, mi familia.
你永远都与我同在
You'll always be with me.
你永远都是我的兄弟
And you'll always be my brother.
谨以此片献给保罗·沃克
结尾有SSK字幕组特制彩蛋.请跳至2:17:12观赏
感谢Paul  Walker陪我们走过了这14年的漫漫长路.
一路走好，愿来世再见。
——SSK字幕组全体组员敬上
2015.5.13